alikelist.com 2010-10-11

# LikeList - Privacy Policy

LikeList is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. This privacy policy explains when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to our website located at [www.likelist.com](http://www.likelist.com/) (the "LikeList Site"). By using the LikeList Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, as modified from time to time by us. Please carefully review this policy so you understand our data privacy practices.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the LikeList Terms of Use. Your use of the LikeList Site and any personal information you provide on the LikeList Site remains subject to our Terms of Use. Any capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Privacy Policy.

### What is Personal Information? 

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as a name, address, telephone number, email address, or other account number, and information about that individual's activities when directly linked to that person, such as information about his or her use of the LikeList Site. Personal information also includes demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, geographic location and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or customers, from which individual customer identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor the LikeList Site.

### Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It

We collect personal information in a number of ways when you visit our website. For example, we collect personal information when you: (1) register and set up an account, (2) send an Invite (3) Ask others for recommendations or (4) contact us by email for any reason. When you visit our website, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring website, and the time and date of your visit and purchases. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. 

### Sharing of Your Information

In addition, we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process or authorities, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of LikeList, our users, our employees or the public. Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets or acquisition. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information when posting reviews or other content to the LikeList Site, this information may be collected and used by others. You agree that we shall bear no responsibility for any such disclosures. We recommend you be cautious in giving out personal information to others in public online forums.

### Email Tools

If you send emails through our site, your email will include your email address and any personal message you include. However, these emails aren't private communications. We do not retain, in any easily retrievable way, the addresses you are emailing. You may not use these tools to send spam or content that violates the user agreement.

### Communicating with Other Users 

You may not harvest personal data (including email addresses) from the site, and specifically, you may not use email addresses displayed on the site to ask users to join or contribute to your services.

### Security 

We have put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. Your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our website by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.

### Control of Personal Information

We give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and to view, correct or remove your personal information.

  1. If you want to view, correct or remove your personal information, you can access your information online by clicking the "Account" or "Profile" link.

  2. To contact us directly, email LikeList at [customerservice@likelist.com](mailto:customerservice@likelist.com) or write to us at LikeList Inc, 440 N. Wolfe Road, MS-159 Sunnyvale, CA 94085

### Cookies, IP Addresses and URLs

Automatically Collected Information: We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser you use. Information may be automatically collected through the use of "cookies" which are discussed in more detail below. We also collect various types of "clickstream" information which is information about your browsing behavior, such as IP address information, entry and exit points for the Site, search terms, Website addresses you visit, page views, and impressions.

Cookies: Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a website when you visit. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the LikeList Site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit. In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve our site by seeing which areas and features are most popular to personalize the LikeList Site, to improve the site experience and to complete transactions you have requested. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. If you decide not to accept our cookies, you will still be able to access those parts of the LikeList Site available to the general public but you may not be able to use some of the site's features or services, and you may have a less satisfactory experience.

### Use of our Website by Children

We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children's use of the Internet. We do not intend to collect information from children who are under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 you should not provide information on our website.¬† Further, we strongly encourage parents and guardians to supervise the activity of all children under the age of 18. 

### Links to Other Websites

Our website contains links to other websites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Except as described above, we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of websites to which we link. Links from our website to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

### Site Development

THE ALIKELIST SERVICE IS UNDER CONTINUOUS DEVELOPMENT AND TESTING BY ALIKELIST. THE ALIKELIST SERVICE MAY CONTAIN BUGS AND OTHER ERRORS THAT COULD ADVERSELY AFFECT THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE ALIKELIST SERVICE.

### Your Comments or Concerns

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this privacy policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach us at [customerservice@likelist.com](mailto:customerservice@likelist.com), or by mail at LikeList Inc, 440 N. Wolfe Road, MS-159 Sunnyvale, CA 94085

### Data Changes

If you terminate your account or delete/change your data or content, we usually update our live databases immediately. However, some data may update more slowly, and some old data may remain in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to propagate changes to partners who receive your data or content. If your account is being terminated or suspended, we may maintain some data to prevent re-registration.

### Policy Changes

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. We may use personal information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this privacy policy. If our privacy practices change we will post the policy changes to our website and notify you by indicating the date the privacy policy was last updated. We will also provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. We encourage you to check back at our website periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

Last Updated: December, 2009
